Guide to the 2000 Voting Technology Archive.
Voting Technology Archive, 2000
- Series I: 2000 Election Material
  - Subseries A: Florida County Recounts
    - Broward County - Recount Precinct by Precinct (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Broward County - Recount Precinct by Precinct (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Churches (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Calhoun County - Martin Sewell, December 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Calhoun County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Charlotte County - Judy Anderson, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Charlotte County - Under Votes (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Citrus County - Susan Gill, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Citrus County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Clay County - Barbara Kirkman, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Clay County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Collier County - Jennifer Edwards, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Collier County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Collier County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Collier County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Columbia County - Carolyn D. Kirby, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Columbia County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - DeSoto County - Ronald A. Turner, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - DeSoto County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Dixie County - Mae Beville, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Dixie County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Duval County - John Stafford, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Duval County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Duval County - Ballot Review (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Duval County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Duval County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Escambia County - Bonnie M. Jones, December 2000 - March 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Escambia County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Flagler County - Peggy Rae Border, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Flagler County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Franklin County - Doris Shiver Gibbs, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Franklin County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Gadsden County - Denny Hutchinson, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Gadsden County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Gilchrist County - Susan J. Bryant, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Gilchrist County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Glades County - Holly Whiddon, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Glades County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Gulf County - Cora Sue Robinson, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Gulf County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Hamilton County - Carol Tolle, December 2000 - March 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Hamilton County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Hardee County - William "Sonny" Coker, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Hardee County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hendry County - Lucretia A. Strickland, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Hendry County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Hernando County - Ann S. Mau, December 2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Hernando County Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Hernando County Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Highlands County - Joe Campbell, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Highlands County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Highlands County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hillsborough County - Pam Iorio, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Hillsborough County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Holmes County - Debbie Wilcox Morris, Decmeber 2000 - March 2001 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Indian River County - Kay Clem, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Indian River County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Indian River County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Jackson County - Sylvia D. Stephens, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Jackson County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Jefferson County - Donna Sorensen Cocroft, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Jefferson County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - LaFayette County - Lana B. Morgan (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - LaFayette County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Lake County - Emogene W. Stegall, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Lake County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Lee County - Philinda A. Young, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Lee County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Lee County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Leon County - Ion Sancho, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Leon County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Levy County - Connie Asbel, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Levy County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Liberty County, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Liberty County - Ballot Review (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Madison County - Linda T. Howell, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Madison County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Manatee County - Robert (Bob) Sweet, December 2000 - March 2001 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Manatee County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Manatee County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Marion County - Dee Brown, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Marion County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Marion County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Marion County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Martin County - Peggy S. Robins, December 2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Martin County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Martin County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Miami-Dade County - David C. Leahy, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Miami-Dade County - Ballot Review (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Monroe County - Harry Sawyer, Jr., December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Monroe County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Nassau County - Shirley N. King., December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Nassaue County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Nassaue County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Okaloosa County - Patricia M. (Pat) Hollarn, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Okaloosa County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Okeechobee County - Gwen Chandler, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Okeechobee County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Orange County - Bill Cowles, December 2000 - March 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Orange County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Osceola County - Donna Bryant, November 2000 - April 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Osceola County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Osceola County - Ballot Review (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Palm Beach County - Theresa LePore, December 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Palm Beach County - Ballot Reveiw (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Palm Beach County -Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Palm Beach County -Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Palm Beach County -Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Palm Beach County -Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Pasco County - Kurt S. Browning, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Pasco County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Pasco County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Pasco County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Pinellas County - Deborah Clark, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Pinellas County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Pinellas County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Pinellas County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Pinellas County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Pinellas County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Pinellas County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Polk County - Helen B. Gienau, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Polk County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Polk County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Polk County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Putnam County - Donald L. (Don) Hersey, December 2000 - March 2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Putnam County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Santa Rosa County - P. Douglas Wilkes, Jr., December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Santa Rosa County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Sarasota County - Marilyn Gerkin, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Sarasota County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Sarasota County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Sarasota County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Sarasota County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Seminole County - Sandra "Sandy" S. Goard, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Seminole County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Seminole County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Seminole County - Ballot Review (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Seminole County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - St. Johns County - Penny L. Halyburton, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - St. Johns County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - St. Lucie County - Gertrude Walker, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - St. Lucie County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Sumter County - Karen Krauss, Dceember 2000 - April 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sumter County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Suwanee County - Glenda Williams, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Suwanee County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Taylor County - Molly Hendry Lilliott, January 2001 - February 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Taylor County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Union County - Babs R. Montpetit, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Union County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Volusia County - Deanie Lowe, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Volusia County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Volusia County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Volusia County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Volusia County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Wakulla County - Sherida Crum, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Wakulla County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Walton County - Melissa Beasley, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Walton County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Washington County - Carol Finch Griffin, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Washington County - Ballot Review (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Ballot Review (Recount) - Unknown County (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Recount Reports - Various Counties (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Subseries B: Leon County Court Case
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2808, Gore et.al v. Harris et. al., November 27 - December 20, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: Examples of Official General Election Ballots, Florida
    - Examples of Improperly Completed Florida Ballots - Various Counties, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Examples of Official Florida Ballots - Various Counties, November 7, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Official General Election Ballot - Bay County Florida, November 7, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Subseries D: Election Results
    - Volusia County Recount Results, November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Walton County Recount Results, November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Election Results I, November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Election Results II, November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Election Results III, November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Election Results IV (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Broward County Results - Election Results V, November 2000 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Series II: E-voting and the 2004 Election
  The hard copy finding aid enclosed in box 11, folder 1 was created by the collectors and reflects their understanding/intention as to the contents of the E-voting and the 2004 Election series. Its accuracy cannot be guaranteed.
  Click here to view this guide. PDF file.
  - E-voting and the 2000 election finding aid (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Century Foundation: African Americans, Voting Machines, and Spoiled Ballots (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations of the Brennan Center for Justice (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Voting: The 2004 Election and Beyond, September 23, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Election Law and Civil Rights in 2004, September 21, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Voter ID Bill Could Unfairly Target Some, June 13, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - League of Women Voters is Split on Paperless Computer Voting Systems, June 11, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Ballot Problems (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Making it Better: Accessibilityand Voting Technologies (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Appeals Court Blocks Oct. 7 Recall Election, September 15, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - New Florida Vote Scandal Feared, October 26, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 2004: A Report Card, October 22, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Missouri Miseries: The Vote 2004: TCF Coverage of the Issues, October 27, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - NASS Statement on Security of Voting Systems, September 15, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Extended Polling Hours, November 2, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - When Should A Presidential Election Be Over, November 17, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - The Disenfranchisement of Voters Under Legal Gaurdianship, November 17, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Analysis: Fear of Chad Derails Recall, November 17, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Crashing the Parties: The Problem of Ballot Access, September 16, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Repair the Electoral College, October 31, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Voting Machines Per Capita: A Bush vs. Gore Issue?, November 5, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Soldiering Votes, October 8, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Identity Politics, August 16, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Eyes on the Buckeyes, October 26, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Analysis Report of Overvotes and Undervotes for the 2004 Election, January 31, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Meshing the State and Federal Presidential Election, Law: The Need for Reform, November 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Michigan Mischief, October 29, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Representaive Government :Voting Rights, May 4, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Official Ballot, August 7, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - A Zest to Vote, October 7, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Political Incorrectness on Campus, September 15, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - More Trials and Tribulations for Ohio, December 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Problems With Provisional Ballots, November 11, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Playing Games with Democracy, October 19, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Its a Crime to Stop Felons from Voting (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Commentary: Absentee Ballot Design Flaws May Disenfranchise Voters, October 22, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - To Assure Pride and Confidence in Electoral Process, August 1 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - State GOP has 'army' to Fight in Election, June 15, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Election Experts Say More Voting Reforms Needed, November 6, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Congress Called on to Fix Problems, June 12, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Securing the Vote: An Analysis of Election Fraud (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - E-Voting: Nightmare or Nirvana?, June 30, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - FBI Investigates Hack at E-Voting Software Company, Decmber 30, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Feds Want E-Voting Source Code Disclosed, June 8, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - High Hopes for Unscrambling the Vote, June 8, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Internet Election Rule Could be Blocked, March 21, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Poll: E-Voters Not So Afraid of Election Day Hacks, August 3, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Justice O'Conner Defends Bush-Gore Decision, May 23, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Senate Considers IDs for Voters, June 14, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Help America Vote, Novmeber 14, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Laboratories of Democrats, September 23, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - U.S. Department of Justice Civil Rights Division Voting Section: Minority Language Citizens (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Ginsburg Lifts High Court Curtain, Feb. 25, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Farrakahn vs. State of Washington, July 25, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Fairness to Felons: A Push to Enfranchise Prisoners, September 25, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Roe vs. Wade and Bush vs. Gore, May 19, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - We Haven't Seen the Last of Election Litigation, June 10, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - We Haven't Seen the Last of Election Litigation, June 10, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Brief of Amicus Curiae (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - 176,000 Bad Punch Cards Ballots, ACLU Says Ground not Planning to Sue Over Last Votes, October 9, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - A Better Ballot, November 3, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - ADA Checklist for Polling Places, February 4 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - All the Presidents Votes?, October 13, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Americans Give Electronic Voting a Vote of Confidence, May 4, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Secretary of State Kevin Shelley Launches Independent Audit, November 12, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Working Paper, November 18, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Analysis of Voting Data form the Recent Venezuela Referendum, September 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Analysis of an Electronic Voting System, February 27, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - An Election Day Clouded by Doubt, October 27, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Mafia Turns to 3G Video Phone, May 16, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Voting Errors Tallied Nationwide, December 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - CalTech/MIT Voting Technology Project, February 5 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Can Voting Machines be Trusted?, November 11, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Electronic Voting-Evaluating the Threat, March 1993 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Chadless But Clueless, City Council Suffers an Official Tie, March 17, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Clear Sailing in Florida Primaries, September 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Ohio Pulls the Plug on Electronic Voting, January 1, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - California Delays Certification of Some Electronic Voting Machines, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Letter to Dr. Williams (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - All Voting Equipment Used in 2004 Must Be Banned by TGDC VVG, January 17, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Letter to Mr. Bryan Whitener and Member of Technical Guideline (Box 11, Folder 81)